https://www.dremed.com/about/policies

DRE is now Avante Medical Surgical
Visit our new website by using the "Proceed to new URL" button.
News
We're Moving!
Biomedical Services
Services Overview Anesthesia Maintenance Lighting Superstructures Equipment Refurbishing
Ordering from DRE
We will provide a formal, written price quotation confirming an informal verbal or emailed price. This can be communicated by email, fax, or postal mail. Due to the nature of our business, all equipment quoted is subject to availability and/or prior sale.
DRE also works with customers who have medical equipment available for trade-in. Ask your DRE sales representative about this option.
When you are ready to order, please contact us to confirm current prices, payment arrangement, availability, and delivery time of your medical equipment or accessories. Whenever possible, we request a hard copy purchase order to ensure that your order is processed properly.
Warranty Protection
This warranty is given in place of all other warranties, expressed or implied. No statement or claim about the product by an employee, agent, or dealer of DRE shall constitute a warranty by DRE or give rise to any liability or obligation of DRE.
DRE, Inc. warranties its equipment to be free of defects in materials and workmanship under normal use and with appropriate maintenance. Length of warranty varies from product to product, please ask your DRE representative for specific warranty coverage. For plastics, rubber or other expendable items, DRE warrants only that such parts will be free of defects in materials and workmanship at the time of purchase.
We will repair or replace any defective item or parts covered under the warranty that are returned to us within the warranty period. The following information is required: RMA number (call DRE to obtain), a letter stating the problem, serial number, and copy of invoice or, in lieu of invoice, the purchaser's name, date of purchase, phone number and address.
Equipment that has been damaged is excluded from this warranty and will be repaired for a fee. Please contact your freight company to submit any claims for shipping damage.
Please do not have your equipment repaired by a third party without prior written authorization. Doing so may void your original warranty.
Extended Warranty Available
In some areas, where we have properly trained, certified, and equipped Authorized Service Representatives, we may be able to offer you an Extended Warranty for your equipment. Upon expiration of our warranty, you may obtain preventive maintenance and repairs from the original manufacturer or from any organization of your choice.
Return Policy
A Customer Service Representative must authorize all returns and issue an RMA number (Return Merchandise Authorization). The following information should be available:
Reason for return
Product model number and quantity
Customer name and copy of sales order or invoice
Eligibility
Requests for returns due to customer error will only be accepted 30 days after original shipment date (a 40% or more restocking fee will be charged).
Merchandise must be properly packaged in the original shipping carton, if possible, to avoid freight damage. Credit will not be given for items damaged due to improper packaging or freight damage.
Customers must obtain an RMA number from a DRE representative and display this number on the outside of the package.
D.R.E. reserves the right to determine in its sole discretion whether an item will be accepted: as a warranty return, for quality issues, or as damaged goods.
Charges & Handling of Credits
All returns, regardless of whether the returns are determined to be legitimate, are subject to a handling/restocking fee of 40% of the sale price of the item.
All returns are subject to inspection to determine condition of merchandise prior to issuance of credit.
An additional fee of 20% of the original sale price will be charged for returned items that contain customer markings, stickers, or require repackaging to be returned to saleable condition.
Freight/shipping charges associated with the returned merchandise from the original order will not be credited. Freight for returned merchandise must be shipped pre-paid freight (collect shipments will be refused).
Privacy Policy
We are committed to protecting your privacy. Any personal information provided to DRE, Inc. will not be sold nor given to any third party.
Information We Collect
We collect information you supply, such as your name, email address, telephone number, and credit card. We encrypt sensitive information.
We use information collected from cookies and other technologies, such as pixel tags, to help us measure traffic and usage. This allows us to automatically collect and store certain information, including details of how you used our site, such as browser type, browser language, your search queries, the date and time of your request and referral URL, and telephone log information like your phone number, time and date of calls, duration of calls.
How We Use This Information
We may use this information for promotional emails or remarketing ads. We will give you the chance to refuse (or unsubscribe from) any marketing email from us in the future.
We also use collected information for remarketing advertisements, to serve ads across the Internet based on past visits to our website. Our ad content will not imply knowledge of personally identifiable or sensitive information.
You can browse websites with cookies switched off (and/or block third party cookies) by adjusting your web browser settings or preferences. You can also use your web browser's settings or preferences to remove your cookies at any time, and some browsers will also have a setting that will enable them to be automatically deleted when you close it.
Legal Disclosures
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Website.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
We will ask for your consent before using information for a purpose other than those that are set out in this privacy policy.
We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time. If we make material changes to this policy, we will post them here.
Listing Disclaimer
Stock & Inventory
DRE lists popular medical and surgical equipment in the marketplace. Our factory new items are usually available and in stock. Because of frequent changes in supply and demand, the current inventory of used and refurbished items are evaluated on a quote by quote basis. Our staff will check DRE inventory as well as availability from other industry partners. If the specific item you request is not in stock or available we will quote a suitable replacement for the item.
Product Information
Items listed on the website are for informational purposes only. Although we intend to keep up to date information, occasionally information that needs to be updated will remain on the site. The product description is not intended to match the exact configuration and options that will be quoted by your sales representative. Please base your purchasing decision on specific information you receive from your sales representative.
Pictures
The picture shown is a representation of the product, not the actual product in stock. If you would like an actual picture of the product please arrange this with your sales representative.
Menu
Products
Support
Español
Medical Equipment
Medical Specialties
Services
Medical Supplies
Need Help?
Call a DRE Sales Expert.
Pulse Oximeters (SpO2)
Need Help?
Call a DRE Sales Expert.
(502) 244-6333
Need Help?
Call a OR Supply Sales Expert.
Forgot your password?
Remember me
Log me in!
